Preface:
	The goal of this project is to give a free, useful tool for all people around the Earth, regardless of their operating system.
	Before the usage of this tool you need to check if the directories that you want to syncronize don't contain the files with names more that 256 characters. You can do this with the utility FindLongPath.
	Also before the usage of this tool you need to obtain layout of the start points with utility GetFilesMetadata.

Description:
	This project is aimed to syncronize files from two start points. Start point is a directory from which the syncronization of files is done. For example, you have two directories with plenty of files (like "/usr/main" and "/usr/backup", or "C:/usr/main" and "C:/usr/backup"). And some of these cases:
1) "usr/main" contains the fresh (current) versions of files, and "usr/backup" contains old versions of the same files
2) "usr/main" contains the renamed and relocated versions of files, and you want the same arrangement "usr/backup"
3) "usr/main" contains some new files that "usr/backup" doesn't.
4) part of files in "usr/main" suddenly became corrupted, and you want to compare them with those in "usr/backup" and recover what is necessary.
this program will help to handle these tasks. You just need two files describing contents of corresponding start points - main and backup, each with the following format:

start point

filename
relative path
20-bytes hash

filename
relative path
20-bytes hash

and so on

put differently, you need two results of execution of my another project - GetFilesMetadata.


Input:
To start the program, enter in command line:
SynchronizeData <config file>
The config file must be UTF16LE (2-byte unicode little endian) file, containing the following arguments, each per line, in the fixed order:
main metadata file
backup metadata file

Output:
1) Files in backup must be renamed and relocated in accordance to the same (by contents) files in main.
2) New files in main that are not in backup, are copied in backup at the same relative (to start point) locations.

3) Pairs of files with the same names and relative paths, but not the same contents, are written into the file "probably corrupted.txt" in the next format:
probably corrupted file in main 1
probably corrupted file in backup 1

probably corrupted file in main 2
probably corrupted file in backup 2

and so on

You need to check these pairs.
If you check the pair and see that file somewhere is really corrupted, handle situation as it seem relevant to you.
If you see that files aren't corrupted, and the file in main is just a newer version of the same file in backup, don't delete the strings - leave them in the file. This file can be later used to copy-with-replace files from main into backup with the utility CopyFiles. Just make sure that among the left pairs there is no pair in which one of the files is actually corrupted.

4) Files that exist in backup but not exist in main are written into the file "supposedly deleted from main.txt". Handle those files as it seem relevant to you

5) Files that weren't copied because of some unknown reason are written into the file "not copied.txt". This file appears only if something went wrong. Normally you won't see it after execution